Painting Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Painting Flanders (Box 26)
  - MEMLING, Hans, ca. 1430-1494 (Box 33–34)
    - Venice (Box 34)
    - Vicenza (Box 34)
    - Washington (Box 34)
  - MOMPER, Joos de, 1564-1635 (Box 34)
  - MORO, Antonio, 1512-1576 (Box 34)
    - Amsterdam (Box 34)
    - Chicago (Box 34)
    - Eindhoven (Box 34)
    - Madrid (Box 34)
    - Munich (Box 34)
    - New York (Box 34)
    - Washington (Box 34)
  - NIEULANDT, Adriaen van (Box 34)
  - ORLEY, Bernaert van, ca. 1492-ca. 1541 (Box 34)
  - PATINIR, Joachim, ca. 1480-before 1524 (Box 34)
  - PEREYNS, Simon (Box 35)
  - POURBUS, Franz, the younger, 1569-1622 (Box 35)
    - Paris (Box 35)
  - ROMBOUTS, Th. (Box 35)
  - ROYMERSWAELE, Marines van, 1497-1567 (Box 35)
  - RUBENS, Peter Paul, 1577-1640 (Box 35)
    - Drawings (Box 35)
      - Amsterdam (Box 35)
      - Antwerp (Box 35)
      - Bayonne (Box 35)
      - Berlin (Box 35)
      - Besancon (Box 35)
      - Brunswick (Box 35)
      - Cambridge (Box 35)
      - Chatsworth (Box 35)
      - Cleveland (Box 35)
      - Edinburgh (Box 35)
      - Haarlem (Box 35)
      - Leipzig (Box 35)
      - Leningrad (Box 35)
      - London (Box 35–36)
        - British Museum (Box 36)
        - Victoria and Albert Museum (Box 36)
        - Private Collection (Box 36)
      - Montpellier (Box 36)
      - Munich (Box 36)
      - New York (Box 36)
      - Oslo (Box 36)
      - Paris (Box 36)
        - Louvre (Box 36)
          - Battle of Anghiari Drawing (Box 36)
        - Institut Neerlandais (Collection of Lugt) (Box 36)
      - Rotterdam (Box 36)
      - Stettin (Box 36)
      - Stockholm (Box 36)
      - Vienna (Box 36)
      - Weimar (Box 36)
    - Paintings (Box 37)
      - Althorphouse (Box 37)
      - Amsterdam (Box 37)
      - Antwerp (Box 37)
      - Berlin (Box 37)
      - Boston (Box 37)
      - Brussels (Box 37)
      - Cambridge (Box 37)
      - Chicago (Box 37)
      - Cleveland (Box 37)
      - Copenhagen (Box 37)
      - Dresden (Box 37)
      - Genoa (Box 37)
      - Glen Falls (Box 37)
      - Grasse (Box 37)
      - Groningen (Box 37)
      - Hartford (Box 38)
      - Leningrad (Box 38)
        - Hermitage (Box 38)
      - London (Box 38)
        - National Gallery (Box 38)
        - Whitehall (Box 38)
      - Madrid (Box 38)
        - Diana, Nymphs, and Fauns (Box 38)
        - Garden of Love (Box 38)
      - Munich (Box 38)
      - New Haven (Box 38)
      - New York (Box 38)
        - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 38)
      - Oxford (Box 38)
      - Paris (Box 38)
        - Louvre (Box 38)
          - Marie d' Medici Series (Box 38–39)
      - Rome (Box 39)
      - Rotterdam (Box 39)
      - Stockholm (Box 39)
      - Vaduz (Box 39)
      - Venice (Box 39)
      - Vienna (Box 39)
      - Washington (Box 39)
  - SADELER, Aegideus (Box 39)
  - SAVERY, Roelant, 1576-1639 (Box 39)
  - SCROTS, William, fl. 1537-1554 (Box 39)
  - SITHIUM, Miguel, 1469-1525 (Box 39)
  - SNYPER, Frans, 1579-1657 (Box 39)
  - SOMER, Paulus van, I, 1576-1621 (Box 39)
  - SPRANGER, Bartholomaeus, 1546-1611 (Box 39)
  - STRAET, Jan van der] Stradanus, 1523-1605 (Box 39)
  - SUSTERMANS, Justus (Box 39)
  - SWART van Groningen, Jan, ca. 1500-1560 (Box 39)
  - TENIERS, David II, 1610-1690 (Box 39–40)
    - Madrid (Box 40)
    - Paris (Box 40)
    - Vienna (Box 40)
  - UTENS, Giusto, d. ca. 1609 (Box 40)
  - VAILLANT, Wallerant, 1623-1677 (Box 40)
  - VALCKENBORCH (Box 40)
  - VAN DER WEYDEN, Rogier, ca. 1399-1464 (Box 40)
    - Antwerp (Box 40)
    - Beaune (Box 40)
    - Berlin (Box 40)
    - Cambridge (Box 40)
    - Brussels (Box 40)
    - Frankfurt (Box 40)
    - Madrid (Box 40)
    - Munich (Box 40)
    - New York (Box 41)
    - Paris (Box 41)
    - Vienna (Box 41)
    - Washington (Box 41)
  - VAN DYCK, Anthony, 1599-1641 (Box 41)
    - Drawings (Box 41)
      - Chatsworth (Box 41)
    - Paintings (Box 41)
      - Amsterdam (Box 41)
      - Antwerp (Box 41)
      - Bayonne (Box 41)
      - Birmingham (Box 41)
      - Boston (Box 41)
      - Brussels (Box 41)
      - Dresden (Box 42)
      - Genoa (Box 42)
      - Hampton Court (Box 42)
      - London (Box 42)
      - Madrid (Box 42)
      - Munich (Box 42)
      - New York (Box 42)
        - Frick Collection (Box 42)
        - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 42)
      - Paris (Box 42)
      - Saventhem (Box 42)
      - Turin (Box 42)
      - Vienna (Box 42)
      - Washington (Box 42–43)
      - Windsor (Box 43)
  - VAN EYCK, Hubert, d. 1426 (Box 43)
  - VAN EYCK, Jan, ca. 1390-1441 (Box 43)
    - Antwerp (Box 43)
    - Berlin (Box 43)
    - Bruges (Box 43)
    - Budapest (Box 43)
    - Dresden (Box 43)
    - Frankfurt (Box 43)
    - London (Box 43)
      - National Gallery (Box 43)
    - Louvain (Box 44)
    - Madrid (Box 44)
    - New York (Box 44)
    - Paris (Box 44)
    - Vienna (Box 44)
  - VAN EYCK, Hubert and Jan (Box 44)
    - Ghent Altarpiece (Box 44)
      - Altarpiece Closed (Box 44)
        - Donors (Box 44)
        - Annunciation (Box 44)
      - Altarpiece Open (Box 44)
        - Adam and Eve (Box 44)
        - Adoration of the Lamb (Box 44)
        - Angel Singers and Musicians (Box 44)
        - Hermit Saints and Pilgrim Saints (Box 44)
        - Just Judges and Christ's Soldiers (Box 44)
        - Virgin, Christ, and S. John (Box 44)
  - VERMEYEN, Jan, ca. 1500-ca. 1559 (Box 44)
  - VOS, Cornelis de (Box 45)
  - VOS, Maarten de, 1532-1603 (Box 45)
  - WIERIX, Hieronymus, ca. 1548-1619 (Box 45)
  - WITTE, Pieter de, 1548-1628 (Box 45)
- Painting France (Box 45)
  - Romanesque (Box 45)
    - Berze-La-Ville (Box 45)
    - Le Puy (Box 45)
      - S. Michel (Box 45)
    - Maureillas (Box 45)
      - S. Martin de Fenouillard (Box 45)
    - Montmorillon (Box 45)
    - Poitiers (Box 45)
      - Baptistry (Box 45)
    - S. Ceneri (Box 45)
    - S. Jacques les Guerets (Box 45)
    - S. Loup de Naud (Box 45)
    - S. Savin (Box 45)
      - Abbey Church (Box 45)
        - Crypt (Box 45)
        - Nave (Box 45)
        - Porch (Box 45)
    - Tavant (Box 45–46)
    - Vicq (Box 46)
  - Gothic (Box 46)
    - 13th century (Box 46)
    - 14th century (Box 46)
      - Antwerp (Box 46)
      - Avignon (Box 46)
      - Bagnot (Box 46)
      - Florence (Box 46)
      - Paris (Box 46)
        - Musee du Cluny (Box 46)
        - Louvre (Box 46)
          - Paremont de Narbonne (Box 46)
      - Troyes (Box 46)
    - 15th century (Box 46)
      - Amiens (Box 46)
      - Avignon (Box 46)
      - La Chaise Dieu (Box 46)
      - Chicago (Box 46)
      - London (Box 46–47)
      - New York (Box 47)
      - Paris (Box 47)
        - Louvre (Box 47)
          - Avignon Pieta (Box 47)
      - S Floret le Chateau (Puy de Dome) (Box 47)
      - Master of Moulins (Box 47)
        - Autun (Box 47)
        - Brussels (Box 47)
        - Chantilly (Box 47)
        - Chicago (Box 47)
        - Moulins (Box 47)
        - Munich (Box 47)
        - New York (Box 47)
        - Paris (Box 47)
      - Master of the Parlement of Paris Altar (Box 47)
      - Master of S. Giles (Box 47)
      - Master of S. Jean de Luz, ca. 1475 (Box 47)
      - Master of S. Sebastian (Box 47–48)
    - 16th century (Box 48)
      - School of Fontainbleau (Box 48)
    - 17th century, 18th century (Box 48)
    - 19th century (Box 48)
      - French Academy (Box 48)
    - 20th century (Box 48)
    - ARP, Hans, 1886-1966 (Box 48)
    - AUBERT, Jean, 1824-1906 (Box 48)
    - AUJAME, Jean (Box 48)
    - ALED, J.A.J.C., 1702-1766 (Box 48)
    - BALTHUS, 1910- (Box 48)
    - BASHKIRTSEFF, Marie, 1860-1884 (Box 48)
    - BASTIEN-LEPAGE, Jules, 1848-1884 (Box 48)
    - BAUCHANT, Andre, 1873- (Box 48)
    - BAUDRY, Paul, 1828-1886 (Box 48)
    - BAUGIN, Lubit (Box 48)
    - BAZAINE, Jean, 1904- (Box 49)
    - BAZILLE, Frederic, 1841-1870 (Box 49)
    - BEAUDIN, Andre, 1895- (Box 49)
    - BEAUMETZ, Jean (Box 49)
    - BEAUNEVEU, Andre (Box 49)
    - BECKER, G. (Box 49)
    - BELLANGE, Jacques, ca. 1575-1616 (Box 49)
    - BELLEGAMBE, Jean, ca. 1475-1535 (Box 49)
    - BENOIST, Antoine (Box 49)
    - BERARD, Christian (Box 49)
    - BERAUD, Jean, 1849-1910 (Box 49)
    - BERNARD, Emile, 1868-1941 (Box 49)
    - BERTHOLLE, Jean (Box 49)
    - BERTHON, R.T., 1776-1859 (Box 49)
    - BERTRAND, Jean, 1823-1889 (Box 49)
    - BESNARD, Albert, 1849-1934 (Box 49)
    - BEZOMBES, Roger (Box 49)
    - BINET, Victor (Box 49)
    - BLANCHARD, Jacques, 1600-1638 (Box 49)
    - BOILLY, Louis, 1761-1845 (Box 49)
    - BOMBOIS, Camille (Box 49)
    - BONHEUR, Rosa, 1822-1899 (Box 49)
    - BONNARD, Pierre, 1867-1947 (Box 49–50)
    - BONNAT, Leon (Box 50)
    - BOUCHER, Francois, 1703-1770 (Box 50)
      - Drawings (Box 50)
      - Paintings (Box 50)
        - Baltimore (Box 50)
        - Boston (Box 50)
        - London (Box 50)
        - Munich (Box 50)
        - New York (Box 50)
        - Orleans (Box 50)
        - Paris (Box 50)
          - Hotel Soubise (Box 50)
          - Louvre (Box 50)
        - Stockholm (Box 50)
        - Washington (Box 50)
    - BOUDIN, Eugene Louis (Box 50–51)
    - BOUGEREAU, William (Box 51)
    - BOULOGNE, Bon, 1649-1777 (Box 51)
    - BOULLOGNE, Louis, the younger, 1654-1733 (Box 51)
    - BOURDICHON, Jean, ca. 1457-1521 (Box 51)
    - BOURDON, Sebastian (Box 51)
    - BRAQUE, Georges, 1882-1963 (Box 51)
      - Basel (Box 51)
      - Berne (Box 51)
      - Chicago (Box 51)
      - London (Box 51)
      - Milford (Box 51)
      - New Haven (Box 51)
      - New York (Box 51–52)
      - Paris (Box 52)
      - Washington (Box 52)
    - BREHAN, Marquise de, fl. 1786-1789 (Box 52)
    - BRETON, Jules (Box 52)
    - BRUANDET, L., 1795-1804 (Box 52)
    - BURNAUD, Eugene (Box 52)
    - CABANEL, Alexandre, 1823-1889 (Box 52)
    - CAILLEBOTTE, Gustave, 1848-1894 (Box 52)
    - CALLET, Antoine-Francois, 1741-1823 (Box 52)
    - CALLOT, Jacques, 1592-1635 (Box 52)
    - CAROLIAS-DURAN, 1837-1917 (Box 52)
    - CARON, Antoine, 1521-1599 (Box 52)
    - CARPEAUX, Jean-Baptiste, 1827-1875 (Box 52)
    - CARRIERE, Eugene, 1849-1906 (Box 52)
    - CAZIN, Jean Charles, 1841-1901 (Box 52)
    - CEZANNE, Paul, 1839-1906 (Box 52)
      - Photographs (Box 53)
      - Drawings (Box 53)
      - Loran Diagrams (Box 53)
      - Paintings (Box 53–54)
        - Ardmore, PA (Box 54)
        - Baltimore (Box 54)
        - Basle (Box 54)
        - Berlin (Box 54)
        - Boston (Box 54)
        - Cambridge (Box 54)
        - Chicago (Box 54)
        - Cleveland (Box 54)
        - London (Box 54)
        - Minneapolis (Box 54)
        - Moscow (Box 54)
        - New York (Box 54–55)
        - Northampton (Box 55)
        - Paris (Box 55)
          - Louvre (Box 55)
        - Philadelphia (Box 55)
        - Prague (Box 55)
        - Washington (Box 55)
        - Weimar (Box 55)
        - Winterthur (Box 56)
        - Worcester (Box 56)
        - Wuppertal (Box 56)
        - Zurich (Box 56)
    - CHABAS, Paul, 1869-1937 (Box 56)
    - CHABAUD, Auguste E., 1882- (Box 56)
    - CHAMPAGNE, Philippe de, 1602-1674 (Box 56)
      - Boston (Box 56)
      - London (Box 56)
      - Paris (Box 56)
    - CHARDIN, Jean-Simeon, 1699-1779 (Box 56)
      - Berlin (Box 56)
      - Boston (Box 56)
      - Leningrad (Box 56)
      - Paris (Box 56)
      - Vienna (Box 56)
      - Washington (Box 57)
    - CHARLET, Nicolas, 1792-1845 (Box 57)
    - CHARMY, Emilie, 1880- (Box 57)
    - CHARONTON, Enguerrand, 1410-1461 (Box 57)
    - CHARPENTIER, C.M. Blondelu (Box 57)
    - CHASSERIAU, Theodore, 1819-1856 (Box 57)
    - CHENAVARD, Paul, 1807-1895 (Box 57)
    - CLAUDE [Gellee] Lorrain, 1604-1682 (Box 57)
      - Drawings (Box 57)
      - Paintings (Box 57)
        - Berlin (Box 57)
        - Boston (Box 57)
        - Buffalo (Box 57)
        - Cleveland (Box 57)
        - Dresden (Box 57)
        - London (Box 57)
        - Munich (Box 58)
        - New York (Box 58)
        - Paris (Box 58)
        - Rome (Box 58)
    - CLODION, Claude, 1738-1814 (Box 58)
    - CLOUET, Francois (Box 58)
      - Drawings (Box 58)
      - Paintings (Box 58)
        - Chantilly (Box 58)
        - New York (Box 58)
        - Paris (Box 58)
        - Washington (Box 58)
    - CLOUET, Jean, ca. 1485-ca. 1540 (Box 58)
      - Paris (Box 58)
    - CLOUET, school of (Box 58)
    - COCTEAU, Jean (Box 58)
    - CONSTANT, Benjamin, 1845-1902 (Box 58)
    - CORMON, Fernand, 1845-1927 (Box 58)
    - CORNEILLE de Lyon (Box 58)
      - New York (Box 58)
    - COROT, Jean Baptiste Camille, 1796-1875 (Box 58)
      - Paintings (Box 59)
        - Boston (Box 59)
        - Chicago (Box 59)
        - Florence (Box 59)
        - Glasgow (Box 59)
        - Hartford (Box 59)
        - London (Box 59)
        - New Haven (Box 59)
        - New York (Box 59)
        - Northampton (Box 59)
        - Paris (Box 59–60)
        - Philadelphia (Box 60)
        - Reims (Box 60)
        - Washington (Box 60)
        - Wellesley (Box 60)
    - COTTET, Charles, 1863-1925 (Box 60)
    - COUDER, Louis C., 1790-1873 (Box 60)
    - COURBET, Gustave, 1819-1877 (Box 60)
      - Cartoons (Box 60)
      - Paintings (Box 60)
        - Besancon (Box 60)
        - Boston (Box 60)
        - Chicago (Box 60)
        - Copenhagen (Box 60)
        - London (Box 60)
        - Montpellier (Box 60)
        - New Haven (Box 60–61)
        - New York (Box 60)
          - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 60)
        - Northampton (Box 60)
        - Paris (Box 60)
          - Louvre (Box 60)
        - Toledo (Box 60)
        - Washington (Box 60)
    - COURTOIS, Guillaume, 1628-1679 (Box 60)
    - COURTOIS, Jacques, 1621-1675 (Box 60)
    - COUSIN, Jean, the elder, ca. 1500-ca. 1560 (Box 60)
    - COUTURE, Thomas, 1815-1879 (Box 60)
    - COYPEL, Antoine, 1661-1722 (Box 60)
    - COYPEL, Charles Antoine, 1694-1752 (Box 60)
    - COYPEL, Noel, 1628-1707 (Box 60)
    - COYPEL, Noel Nicholas, 1692-1735 (Box 60)
    - DAGNAN-BOUVERET, 1852-1929 (Box 60)
    - DANTAN, Joseph Edward, 1848-1897 (Box 61)
    - DAUBIGNY, Charles Francois, 1817-1878 (Box 62)
    - DAUMIER, Honore, 1808-1879 (Box 62)
      - Drawings (Box 62)
      - Paintings (Box 62)
        - Berlin (Box 62)
        - Essen (Box 62)
        - London (Box 62)
        - Munich (Box 62)
        - New York (Box 62)
        - Paris (Box 62)
        - Philadelphia (Box 62)
        - Washington (Box 62)
    - DAVID, Jacques-Louis, 1748-1825 (Box 62)
      - Drawings (Box 62–63)
      - Paintings (Box 63)
        - Avignon (Box 63)
        - Brussels (Box 63)
        - Cleveland (Box 63)
        - Le Mans (Box 63)
        - London (Box 63)
        - Nantes (Box 63)
        - New York (Box 63)
        - Paris (Box 63)
          - Louvre (Box 63)
            - Coronation of Josephine (Box 63)
            - Helen and Paris (Box 63)
            - Oath of the Horatii (Box 63)
            - Rape of the Sabines (Box 63)
            - Portraits (Box 63)
              - Mme. Recamier (Box 63)
        - Toledo (Box 64)
        - Versailles (Box 64)
        - Vienna (Box 64)
    - DEBAT-PONSAN (Box 64)
    - DEBUCOURT, Louis, 1755-1832 (Box 64)
    - DECAMPS, Alexander G., 1803-1860 (Box 64)
    - DECREUX, Joseph, 1737-1802 (Box 64)
    - DEGAS, Edgar, 1834-1917 (Box 64)
      - Drawings (Box 64)
        - Chicago (Box 64)
        - New York (Box 64)
        - Paris (Box 64)
      - Paintings (Box 64)
        - Berlin (Box 65)
        - Boston (Box 65)
        - Cambridge (Box 65)
        - Chicago (Box 65)
        - Cleveland (Box 65)
        - Hartford (Box 65)
        - London (Box 65)
        - Minneapolis (Box 65)
        - New Haven (Box 65)
        - New York (Box 65)
        - Northampton (Box 65)
        - Paris (Box 65)
          - Louvre (Box 65–66)
          - Luxembourg (Box 66)
        - Philadelphia (Box 66)
        - Providence (Box 66)
        - Washington (Box 66)
    - DELACROIX, Eugene, 1798-1863 (Box 66)
      - Drawings (Box 66)
      - Paintings (Box 66)
        - Baltimore (Box 66)
        - Bordeaux (Box 66)
        - Chicago (Box 66)
        - Leningrad (Box 66)
        - Lille (Box 66)
        - Montpellier (Box 66)
        - Nantua (Box 66)
        - New Haven (Box 66)
        - New York (Box 66)
        - Orgemont (Box 66)
        - Paris (Box 67)
          - Louvre (Box 67)
            - Algerian Woman (Box 67)
            - Crusaders Capture Constantinople (Box 67)
            - Death of Sardanapalus (Box 67)
            - Liberty Leading the People (Box 67)
            - Massacre at Scio (Chios) (Box 67)
            - Self-Portrait (Box 67)
            - Shipwreck of Don Juan (Box 67)
          - Palais Bourbon: Chambre des Deputies: Library (Box 67)
            - Library: Orpheus Mural (Box 67)
            - Library: Attila Mural (Box 67)
            - Library: Pendentive Murals (Box 67–68)
          - Palais Bourbon: Salon du Roi (Box 68)
        - Versailles (Box 68)
        - Washington (Box 68)
        - Winterthur (Box 68)
    - DELAROCHE, Paul, 1797-1856 (Box 68)
    - DELAUNAY, Robert, 1885-1941 (Box 68)
    - DENIS, Maurice, 1870-1943 (Box 68)
    - DERAIN, Andre, 1880-1954 (Box 68)
      - Chambourcy (Box 68)
      - Chicago (Box 68)
      - Paris (Box 68)
      - Troyes (Box 68–69)
      - Washington (Box 69)
    - DERUET, Claude (Box 69)
    - DESPORTES, Francois, 1661-1743 (Box 69)
    - DESVALLIERES, Georges, 1861- (Box 69)
    - DETAILLE, Jean Baptiste Edouard, 1848-1912 (Box 69)
    - DIAZ DE LA PENA, Narcisse, ca. 1808-1876 (Box 69)
    - DORE, Gustave, 1832-1883 (Box 69)
    - DROUAIS, Francois Herbert, 1727-1775 (Box 69)
    - DUBOIS, Ambroise, 1543-1614 (Box 69)
    - DUBOIS-PILLET, A., 1846-1890 (Box 69)
    - DUBREUIL, Toussant, 1561-1602 (Box 69)
    - DUBUFFET, Jean, 1901-1965 (Box 69)
    - DUCHAMP, Marcel, 1887-1968 (Box 69)
    - DUCREUX, Joseph, 1737-1802 (Box 69)
    - DUFY, Raoul, 1880- (Box 69–70)
    - DUGHET, Gaspard, 1615-1675 (Box 70)
    - DUMAS, M.R., 1812-1885 (Box 70)
    - DUMONT, Jacques, 1761-1844 (Box 70)
    - DUMOUSTIER, Daniel, 1574-1646 (Box 70)
    - DUMOUSTIER, Etienne (Box 70)
    - DUPLESIS, Joseph, 1725-1802 (Box 70)
    - DUPRE, Jules, 1811-1889 (Box 70)
    - ESTEVE, Maurice, 1904- (Box 70)
    - FAIVRE, Jules Abel, 1867- (Box 70)
    - FALERO (Box 70)
    - FANTIN-LATOUR, Henri, 1836-1904 (Box 70)
      - Chicago (Box 70)
      - Cleveland (Box 70)
      - Paris (Box 70)
      - St. Louis (Box 70)
      - Washington (Box 70)
    - FAUTRIER, Jean, 1898-1964 (Box 70)
    - FLANDRIN, Hippolyte-Jean, 1809-1864 (Box 70)
    - FONTENAY, Jean Bellin de, 1653-1715 (Box 70)
    - FORAIN, Jean Louis, 1852-1931 (Box 70)
    - FOUQUET, Jean, ca. 1420-ca. 1481 (Box 70)
      - Antwerp (Box 70)
      - Berlin (Box 70)
      - Loches (Box 70)
      - Marseilles (Box 70)
      - Nouans (Box 70)
      - Paris (Box 70)
      - Vienna (Box 70)
    - FRAGONARD, Alexander Evariste, 1780-1850 (Box 71)
    - FRAGONARD, Jean-Honore, 1732-1806 (Box 71)
      - Drawings (Box 71)
      - Paintings (Box 71)
        - Besancon (Box 71)
        - Leningrad (Box 71)
        - London (Box 71)
        - Madrid (Box 71)
        - New York (Box 71)
          - Frick Collection (Box 71)
        - Oyster Bay, NY (Box 71)
        - Paris (Box 71)
          - Louvre (Box 72)
        - Washington (Box 72)
        - Zurich (Box 72)
    - FREMINET, Martin, 1567-1619 (Box 72)
    - FRESNAYE, Roger de la, 1885-1925 (Box 72)
    - FRIESZ, Othon (Box 72)
    - FROMENT, N. (Box 72)
    - FROMENTIN, Eugene, 1820-1876 (Box 72)
    - GAILLAC (Box 72)
    - GARNIER, Jules Arsene, 1847-1889 (Box 72)
    - GAUDIER-BRZESKA, Henri, 1891-1915 (Box 72)
    - GAUGUIN, Paul, 1848-1903 (Box 72)
      - Paintings (Box 72–73)
        - Basle (Box 73)
        - Boston (Box 73)
        - Brussels (Box 73)
        - Cleveland (Box 73)
        - Copenhagen (Box 73)
        - Essen (Box 73)
        - Kansas City (Box 73)
        - Moscow (Box 73)
        - New York (Box 73)
          - Stransky Collection (Box 73)
        - Paris (Box 73)
        - Stockholm (Box 73)
        - Washington (Box 74)
        - Worcester (Box 74)
    - GERARD, Francois, 1770-1837 (Box 74)
      - Paris (Box 74)
    - GERARD, Marguerite, 1761-1837 (Box 74)
    - GERICAULT, Theodore, 1791-1824 (Box 74)
      - Drawings (Box 74)
      - Paintings (Box 74)
        - Baltimore (Box 74)
        - Cambridge (Box 74)
        - Chicago (Box 74)
        - Ghent (Box 74)
        - Lyon (Box 74)
        - Northampton (Box 74)
        - Paris (Box 74)
          - Louvre (Box 74)
            - Epsom Races (Box 74)
            - Officer of the Cuirassiers (Box 74)
            - Raft of the Medusa (Box 74)
        - Stockholm (Box 74)
    - GEROME, Jean-Leon, 1824-1904 (Box 74–75)
    - GILLOT, Claude, 1673-1722 (Box 75)
    - GIMEL, George, 1898- (Box 75)
    - GIRODET DE ROUCY-TRIOSON, Anne-Louis, 1767-1824 (Box 75)
    - GLEIZES, Albert Leon, 1881-1953 (Box 75)
      - New York (Box 75)
    - GLEYRE (Box 75)
    - GRANET, Francois-Marius, 1775-1849 (Box 75)
    - GREUZE, Jean-Baptiste, 1725-1805 (Box 75)
      - Drawings (Box 75)
      - Paintings (Box 75)
        - London (Box 75–76)
        - Montpellier (Box 76)
        - New York (Box 76)
        - Paris (Box 76)
          - Louvre (Box 76)
            - Broken Pitcher (Box 76)
        - Stockholm (Box 76)
        - Washington (Box 76)
    - GROMAIRE, Marcel (Box 76)
    - GROS, Antoine-Jean, 1771-1835 (Box 76)
      - Bordeaux (Box 76)
      - Detroit (Box 76)
      - Paris (Box 76)
        - Louvre (Box 76)
          - Battle of Eylau (Box 76)
          - Pest House at Jaffa (Box 76)
      - Toulouse (Box 76)
      - Versailles (Box 76)
    - GUERIN, Pierre Narciss, 1774-1833 (Box 76)
    - GUILLONNET, O.D.V. (Box 76)
    - GUYS, Constantin, 1805-1892 (Box 77)
    - HALLE, Claude Guy, 1652-1736 (Box 77)
    - HALLE, Noel (Box 77)
    - HENNER, Jean Jacques (Box 77)
    - HENRY-MARTIN, Jean G., 1860- (Box 77)
    - HERAUT, Henri (Box 77)
    - HERBIN, Auguste, 1882-1960 (Box 77)
    - HERSENT, Louis, 1777-1860 (Box 77)
    - HOEY, Nicholas de (Box 77)
    - HOUASSE, Rene Antoine, 1664-1710 (Box 77)
    - HUET, Paul, 1833-1869 (Box 77)
    - HUGO, Victor (Box 77)
    - INGRES, Jean-Auguste-Dominique, 1780-1867 (Box 77)
      - Drawings (Box 77)
      - Portraits (Box 77–78)
        - Guillon Lethiere Family (Box 78)
      - Paintings (Box 78)
        - Aix-en-Provence (Box 78)
        - Bayonne (Box 78)
        - Boston (Box 78)
        - Brussels (Box 78)
        - Cambridgec (Box 78)
        - Florence (Box 78)
        - Liege (Box 78)
        - London (Box 78)
        - Montauban (Box 78)
        - Montpellier (Box 78)
        - Nantes (Box 78)
        - Northampton (Box 78)
        - Paris (Box 78–79)
          - Louvre (Box 79)
            - Apotheosis of Homer (Box 79)
            - Bagneuse de Valpincon (Box 79)
            - Odalisque (Box 79)
            - Oedipus and the Sphinx (Box 79)
            - The Source (Box 79)
            - Turkish Women at the Bath (Box 79)
            - Portraits (Box 79)
              - M. Bertin (Box 79)
              - Mlle. Riviere (Box 79)
              - Mme. Riviere (Box 79)
              - Philibert Riviere (Box 79)
        - Toulouse (Box 79)
    - ISABEY, Eugene, 1803-1886 (Box 79)
    - ISABEY, Jean-Baptiste, 1767-1855 (Box 79)
    - ISABEY, Jean-Baptiste, 1767-1855 (Box 79)
    - IVERNY, J. (Box 79)
    - JACQUE, Chales Emile, 1813-1894 (Box 79)
    - JAMIN, Paul (Box 79)
    - JENNERET, Chales Edouard (SEE LECORBUSIER) (Box 79)
    - JOUVENET, Jean, 1644-1717 (Box 79)
    - LA FAGE, Nicholas (Box 79)
    - LA FOSSE, Charles de, 1636-1716 (Box 79)
    - LA GRENEE, L.J.F., the elder (Box 79)
    - LA GRENEE, J.J., the younger (Box 79)
    - LA HYRE, Laurent de, 1600-1656 (Box 79)
      - Paris (Box 79)
    - LAMBERT-RUCKI, Jean (Box 80)
    - LAMI, Eugene Louis, 1800-1890 (Box 80)
    - LANCRET, Nicolas, 1690-1749 (Box 80)
      - Drawings (Box 80)
      - Paintings (Box 80)